earningguys.com 2018-02-13

# Privacy Policy for EarningGuys.com

At EarningGuys.com your privacy is of utmost importance to us. We do not gather any information regarding our users like their phone no., Social Security numbers, Bank Account No. and nor any credit card information. We only collect information when you subscribe our newsletter or send in your response to a survey.

 **Log Files**

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer’s domain name, but not the e-mail address. We create a log file which contains your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

The information we collect is used to improve the content, layout, and usability of our website. This information is not sold to anyone, including commercial partners.

 **Security**

EarningGuys.com does not collect any sensitive data like credit card information or Social Security numbers and therefore offers a significantly reduced incentive for data theft; we take very seriously our responsibility to protect your private information.

 **Third Party Ads**

EarningGuys.com works with third parties to serve ads and promotions through this site as well as to assist us in managing customer information and to communicate with you. To find out more about how these third parties manage the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please visit the privacy policy on their web sites.

When you are accessing EarningGuys.com you may promotion through an advertising vehicle, and are asked for personal information, you are not sharing that information with EarningGuys.com. Promotions, surveys and other sweepstakes offerings may be sponsored, or co-sponsored, by another company. Some or all of the data collected during such a program may be shared with the marketing partner. Your participation is always voluntary.

 **Email Addresses**

When you make a comment or contact us using the contact page your email id is required. Please be assured that your email address will only be used for responding to your email or comment and will never be made publicly available. We will never sell your email address to any third parties, ever.

 **Comments Policy**

We Welcome comments on our website this requires your Name and Email address. We do not sell or miss use this data. We reserve the right to remove any comment that is not suitable for publication. This could include but is not limited to objectionable and abusive comments. Hate, racist comments, or any other form of prejudice will be removed and the comment poster will be banned!  
Comments made for sole purpose of getting backlinks or advertizing your/any product will not be accepted. Link to third party website will require moderation and we reserve the rights to edit/delete such links.

Spam in any form will not be accepted and will be deleted immediately. We may take action against such spammers.

 **RSS Feed**

When you subscribe for our RSS Feed on your Email we collect your Email address. Your email id is just used for sending you the latest post on our Website. Feeds email is send automatically whenever there is new post on our website. We do not sell or misuse your email id and nor send you spam messages.

 **Links**

This website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we “EarningGuys.com” is not responsible for the privacy policy of other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you reach to other Website read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

Our website contains external links to commercial partners. We are not responsible for the content of these websites, nor their privacy practices. Please refer to the privacy policy listed on their website to find out more information about what information they collect and how they use it.

 **Copyrights**

We take lot of caution has been taken to make sure that there are no copyright infringements in terms of the multimedia content and the subject matter that is posted in this blog. If we use the multimedia content like images or Video we link back to the original owner of the content. We do not represent that content as our own property. If you find anything that could be considered a violation of the copyright norms, please contact us immediately.

 **Notification of Changes**

EarningGuys.com may from time to time, amend this Policy, in whole or in part, at its sole discretion. If there are material changes to this Policy or in how EarningGuys.com uses your personally identifiable information, EarningGuys.com will prominently post such changes with a notice on the homepage of the website prior to implementing the change. Please check this page periodically for changes. Continued use of this site following notification of a change in privacy policy shall constitute acceptance of the change and this Policy.

 **Disclaimer**

Many time on our Website we use the name of other companies and product like Microsoft, iPad, Apple, iPhone, Samsung etc this does not mean that we own or we have the right on the name or product. All name and products are property of their respected owner. All trademark and copyrights are on the name of respected owner and we do not claim as our own.

Further we would like to emphasize that the earning tips given on our blog is purely a personal opinion and should not be taken as a advice. Neither EarningGuys.com nor its owner holds any responsibility whatsoever for your decisions and also on the financial outcome resulting on the advice rendered on EarningGuys.com. The ideas expressed on EarningGuys.com are our own views and should not be taken as recommendations in any way.
